<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app._global.english">English</string>
    <string name="app._global.french">French</string>
    <string name="app._global.german">German</string>
    <string name="app._global.italian">Italian</string>
    <string name="app._global.portuguese">Portuguese</string>
    <string name="app._global.russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="app._global.spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="app._global.swedish">Swedish</string>
    <string name="app.about.app_hint">Here\'s where you can learn more about Scribe and its community.</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.github">See the code on GitHub</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.mastodon">Follow us on Mastodon</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.matrix">Chat with the team on Matrix</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.share_conjugate">Share Scribe Conjugate</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.share_scribe">Share Scribe</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.title">Community</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.view_apps">View all Scribe apps</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.wikimedia">Wikimedia and Scribe</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.wikimedia.caption">How we work together</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.wikimedia.text_1">Scribe would not be possible without countless contributions by Wikimedia contributors to the many projects that they support. Specifically Scribe makes use of data from the Wikidata Lexicographical data community, as well as data from Wikipedia for each language that Scribe supports.</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.wikimedia.text_2">Wikidata is a collaboratively edited multilingual knowledge graph hosted by the Wikimedia Foundation. It provides freely available data that anyone can use under a Creative Commons Public Domain license (CC0). Scribe uses language data from Wikidata to provide users with verb conjugations, noun-form annotations, noun plurals, and many other features.</string>
    <string name="app.about.community.wikimedia.text_3">Wikipedia is a multilingual free online encyclopedia written and maintained by a community of volunteers through open collaboration and a wiki-based editing system. Scribe uses data from Wikipedia to produce autosuggestions by deriving the most common words in a language as well as the most common words that follow them.</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.app_hints">Reset app hints</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.bug_report">Report a bug</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.email">Send us an email</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.rate_conjugate">Rate Scribe Conjugate</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.rate_scribe">Rate Scribe</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.title">Feedback and support</string>
    <string name="app.about.feedback.version">Version</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.privacy_policy.caption">Keeping you safe</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.privacy_policy.text">Please note that the English version of this policy takes precedence over all other versions.\n\nThe Scribe developers (SCRIBE) built the iOS application "Scribe - Language Keyboards" (SERVICE) as an open-source application. This SERVICE is provided by SCRIBE at no cost and is intended for use as is.\n\nThis privacy policy (POLICY) is used to inform the reader of the policies for the access, tracking, collection, retention, use, and disclosure of personal information (USER INFORMATION) and usage data (USER DATA) for all individuals who make use of this SERVICE (USERS).\n\nUSER INFORMATION is specifically defined as any information related to the USERS themselves or the devices they use to access the SERVICE.\n\nUSER DATA is specifically defined as any text that is typed or actions that are done by the USERS while using the SERVICE.\n\n1. Policy Statement\n\nThis SERVICE does not access, track, collect, retain, use, or disclose any USER INFORMATION or USER DATA.\n\n2. Do Not Track\n\nUSERS contacting SCRIBE to ask that their USER INFORMATION and USER DATA not be tracked will be provided with a copy of this POLICY as well as a link to all source codes as proof that they are not being tracked.\n\n3. Third-Party Data\n\nThis SERVICE makes use of third-party data. All data used in the creation of this SERVICE comes from sources that allow its full use in the manner done so by the SERVICE. Specifically, the data for this SERVICE comes from Wikidata, Wikipedia and Unicode. Wikidata states that, "All structured data in the main, property and lexeme namespaces is made available under the Creative Commons CC0 License; text in other namespaces is made available under the Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike License." The policy detailing Wikidata data usage can be found at https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Wikidata:Licensing. Wikipedia states that text data, the type of data used by the SERVICE, "… can be used under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution Share-Alike license". The policy detailing Wikipedia data usage can be found at https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Reusing_Wikipedia_content. Unicode provides permission, "… free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of the Unicode data files and any associated documentation (the "Data Files") or Unicode software and any associated documentation (the "Software") to deal in the Data Files or Software without restriction…" The policy detailing Unicode data usage can be found at https://www.unicode.org/license.txt.\n\n4. Third-Party Source Code\n\nThis SERVICE was based on third-party code. All source code used in the creation of this SERVICE comes from sources that allow its full use in the manner done so by the SERVICE. Specifically, the basis of this project was the project CustomKeyboard by Ethan Sarif-Kattan. CustomKeyboard was released under an MIT license, with this license being available at https://github.com/EthanSK/CustomKeyboard/blob/master/LICENSE.\n\n5. Third-Party Services\n\nThis SERVICE makes use of third-party services to manipulate some of the third-party data. Specifically, data has been translated using models from Hugging Face transformers. This service is covered by an Apache License 2.0, which states that it is available for commercial use, modification, distribution, patent use, and private use. The license for the aforementioned service can be found at https://github.com/huggingface/transformers/blob/master/LICENSE.\n\n6. Third-Party Links\n\nThis SERVICE contains links to external websites. If USERS click on a third-party link, they will be directed to a website. Note that these external websites are not operated by this SERVICE. Therefore, USERS are strongly advised to review the privacy policy of these websites. This SERVICE has no control over and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n\n7. Third-Party Images\n\nThis SERVICE contains images that are copyrighted by third-parties. Specifically, this app includes a copy of the logos of GitHub, Inc and Wikidata, trademarked by Wikimedia Foundation, Inc. The terms by which the GitHub logo can be used are found on https://github.com/logos, and the terms for the Wikidata logo are found on the following Wikimedia page: https://foundation.wikimedia.org/wiki/Policy:Trademark_policy. This SERVICE uses the copyrighted images in a way that matches these criteria, with the only deviation being a rotation of the GitHub logo that is common in the open-source community to indicate that there is a link to the GitHub website.\n\n8. Content Notice\n\nThis SERVICE allows USERS to access linguistic content (CONTENT). Some of this CONTENT could be deemed inappropriate for children and legal minors. Accessing CONTENT using the SERVICE is done in a way that the information is unavailable unless explicitly known. Specifically, USERS "can" translate words, conjugate verbs, and access other grammatical features of CONTENT that may be sexual, violent, or otherwise inappropriate in nature. USERS "cannot" translate words, conjugate verbs, and access other grammatical features of CONTENT that may be sexual, violent, or otherwise inappropriate in nature if they do not already know about the nature of this CONTENT. SCRIBE takes no responsibility for the access of such CONTENT.\n\n9. Changes\n\nThis POLICY is subject to change. Updates to this POLICY will replace all prior instances, and if deemed material will further be clearly stated in the next applicable update to the SERVICE. SCRIBE encourages USERS to periodically review this POLICY for the latest information on our privacy practices and to familiarize themselves with any changes.\n\n10. Contact\n\nIf you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions about this POLICY, do not hesitate to visit https://github.com/scribe-org or contact SCRIBE at scribe.langauge@gmail.com. The person responsible for such inquiries is Andrew Tavis McAllister.\n\n11. Effective Date\n\nThis POLICY is effective as of the 24th of May, 2022.</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party">Third-party licenses</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.author">Author</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.caption">Whose code we used</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.entry_custom_keyboard">Custom Keyboard\n• Author: EthanSK\n• License: MIT\n• Link: https://github.com/EthanSK/CustomKeyboard/blob/master/LICENSE</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.entry_simple_keyboard">Simple Keyboard\n• Author:Simple Mobile Tools\n• License: GPL-3.0\n• Link: https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Keyboard/blob/main/LICENSE</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.license">License</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.link">Link</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.third_party.text">The Scribe developers (SCRIBE) built the iOS application "Scribe - Language Keyboards" (SERVICE) using third party code. All source code used in the creation of this SERVICE comes from sources that allow its full use in the manner done so by the SERVICE. This section lists the source code on which the SERVICE was based as well as the coinciding licenses of each.\n\nThe following is a list of all used source code, the main author or authors of the code, the license under which it was released at time of usage, and a link to the license.</string>
    <string name="app.about.legal.title">Legal</string>
    <string name="app.about.title">About</string>
    <string name="app.conjugate.choose_conjugation.select_tense">Select tense</string>
    <string name="app.conjugate.choose_conjugation.title">Choose a conjugation below</string>
    <string name="app.conjugate.recently_conjugated.title">Recently conjugated</string>
    <string name="app.conjugate.title">Conjugate</string>
    <string name="app.conjugate.verbs_search.placeholder">Search for verbs</string>
    <string name="app.conjugate.verbs_search.title">Conjugate verbs</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_option.conjugate_description">Add new data to Scribe Conjugate.</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_option.conjugate_title">Verb Data</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_option.download_data">Download data</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_option.scribe_description">Add new data to Scribe keyboards.</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_option.scribe_title">Language Data</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_ui.select.all_languages">All languages</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_ui.select.title">Select data to download</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_ui.title">Download Data</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_ui.update_data.check_new">Check for new data</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_ui.update_data.regular_update">Regularly update data</string>
    <string name="app.download.menu_ui.update_data.title">Update data</string>
    <string name="app.installation.app_hint">Follow the directions below to install Scribe keyboards on your device.</string>
    <string name="app.installation.button_quick_tutorial">Quick tutorial</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.keyboard_settings">Open keyboard settings</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.keyboards_bold">Keyboards</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.scribe_settings">Open Scribe settings</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.text_1">Select</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.text_2">Activate keyboards that you want to use</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.text_3">When typing, press</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.text_4">to select keyboards</string>
    <string name="app.installation.keyboard.title">Keyboard installation</string>
    <string name="app.installation.title">Installation</string>
    <string name="app.settings.app_hint">Settings for the app and installed language keyboards are found here.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.button_install_keyboards">Install keyboards</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.annotate_suggestions">Annotate suggest/complete</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.annotate_suggestions_description">Underline suggestions and completions to show their genders as you type.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.auto_suggest_emoji">Autosuggest emojis</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.auto_suggest_emoji_description">Turn on emoji suggestions and completions for more expressive typing.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.default_emoji_tone">Default emoji skin tone</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.default_emoji_tone.caption">Skin tone to be used</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.default_emoji_tone_description">Set a default skin tone for emoji autosuggestions and completions.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.delete_word_by_word">Hold delete is word by word</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.delete_word_by_word_description">Delete text word by word when the delete key is pressed and held.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.double_space_period">Double space periods</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.double_space_period_description">Automatically insert a period when the space key is pressed twice.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.hold_for_alt_chars">Hold for alternate characters</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.hold_for_alt_chars_description">Select alternate characters by holding keys and dragging to the desired character.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.popup_on_keypress">Show popup on keypress</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.popup_on_keypress_description">Display a popup of keys as they\'re pressed</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.punctuation_spacing">Delete punctuation spacing</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.punctuation_spacing_description">Remove excess spaces before punctuation marks.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.functionality.title">Functionality</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.keypress_vibration">Vibrate on key press</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.keypress_vibration_description">Have the device vibrate when keys are pressed.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.default_currency">Default currency symbol</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.default_currency.caption">Symbol for the 123 keys</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.default_currency_description">Select a keyboard layout that suits your typing preference and language needs.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.default_layout">Default keyboard</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.default_layout.caption">Layout to use</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.default_layout_description">Select a keyboard layout that suits your typing preference and language needs.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.disable_accent_characters">Disable accent characters</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.disable_accent_characters_description">Remove accented letter keys on the primary keyboard layout.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.period_and_comma">Period and comma on ABC</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.period_and_comma_description">Include comma and period keys on the main keyboard for convenient typing.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.layout.title">Layout</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.title">Select installed keyboard</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.translation.select_source">Select language</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.translation.select_source.caption">What the source language is</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.translation.select_source.title">Translation language</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.translation.select_source_description">Change the language to translate from.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.keyboard.translation.title">Translation source language</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_color_mode">Dark mode</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_color_mode_description">Change the application display to dark mode.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_language">App language</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_language.caption">Select language for app texts</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_language.one_device_language_warning.message">You only have one language installed on your device. Please install more languages in Settings and then you can select different localizations of Scribe.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_language.one_device_language_warning.title">Only one device language</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.app_language_description">Change which language the Scribe app is in.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.high_color_contrast">High color contrast</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.high_color_contrast_description">Increase color contrast for improved accessibility and a clearer viewing experience.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.increase_text_size">Increase app text size</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.increase_text_size_description">Increase the size of menu texts for better readability.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.menu.title">App settings</string>
    <string name="app.settings.title">Settings</string>
    <string name="app.settings.translation">Translation</string>
    <string name="keyboard.not_in_wikidata.explanation_1">Wikidata is a collaboratively edited knowledge graph that\'s maintained by the Wikimedia Foundation. It serves as a source of open data for projects like Wikipedia and countless others.</string>
    <string name="keyboard.not_in_wikidata.explanation_2">Scribe uses Wikidata\'s language data for many of its core features. We get information like noun genders, verb conjugations and much more!</string>
    <string name="keyboard.not_in_wikidata.explanation_3">You can make an account at wikidata.org to join the community that\'s supporting Scribe and so many other projects. Help us bring free information to the world!</string>
</resources>
